<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Officers on RAGE for ANUSA</title><link>https://rageforanusa.com/role_types/officers/</link><description>Recent content in Officers on RAGE for ANUSA</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 23:25:31 +1000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://rageforanusa.com/role_types/officers/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Ankith Arun Aswath</title><link>https://rageforanusa.com/candidates/ankith/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 23:25:31 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://rageforanusa.com/candidates/ankith/</guid><description>&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h1 id="campaign-summary"&gt;Campaign Summary&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hi everyone, I’m Ankith, and I’m excited to re-nominate as your Parents and Carers’ Officer for 2025! Over the past year, I’ve worked hard to strengthen supports for student parents and carers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A key achievement was negotiating changes to the Parents and Carers Grant, making it $1,000 annually instead of per degree, ensuring fairer access. I also developed the &lt;strong&gt;Parents and Carers Information Hub&lt;/strong&gt;, soon to launch, which will centralize university, city, and federal supports. Alongside this, I’ve initiated collaboration with Carers ACT, continued advocacy around EAPs and ECAs, and worked to improve awareness of carer-friendly spaces on campus.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Chith Weliamuna</title><link>https://rageforanusa.com/candidates/chith/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 23:25:31 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://rageforanusa.com/candidates/chith/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="fighting-for-the-education-you-deserve"&gt;Fighting for the education you deserve&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h2 id="no-cuts"&gt;No cuts&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I will &lt;strong&gt;fight for your education&lt;/strong&gt; by standing against the cuts and advocating to reverse Renew ANU in the relevant fora, as well as continuing to support the student and staff protests.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="better-learning-conditions"&gt;Better learning conditions&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I will &lt;strong&gt;fight for your education&lt;/strong&gt; by:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Advocating for smaller tutorial sizes as classes are overcrowded, and demanding the ANU to release their reasoning for making the classes bigger to begin with.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fighting against the DVCA cuts to speed up student support. You deserve extensions and deferrals on time.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Advocating for a student-centred, clear, forward-thinking and accessible AI policy, building on the Gen-AI report.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expanding book and technology bursaries, and creating a new ANUSA learning materials subsidy for students in STEM and the Arts.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id="accessibility"&gt;Accessibility&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Night-time tutorial options and standardised assessment deadlines for students who work full-time or with other commitments.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;BYOD exams where applicable to improve accessibility and bring ANU exams into the 21st century.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expanding the alternative assessments policy to all parts of ANU to improve accessibility, creativity and fairness. You may find your niche here!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id="fairer-assessments"&gt;Fairer assessments&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Flexible weighting options where applicable so that assessments count in ways that benefit the student the most.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Five day simple extensions with lower late penalties in the interim so that you do not have to endure the cost and anxiety of sourcing a doctor last minute.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;More redemptive measures because failing one assessment should not mean you fail the course. I also support strictly limiting hurdle tasks.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Push for clearer assessment rubrics, appeals processes, and preparatory materials like past exams so you are able to give each task your best shot.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h1 id="delivering-the-services-you-need"&gt;Delivering the services you need&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I will &lt;strong&gt;deliver the services you need by:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Flynn Wade-Schneiders</title><link>https://rageforanusa.com/candidates/flynn/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 23:25:31 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://rageforanusa.com/candidates/flynn/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Kamal Hassan</title><link>https://rageforanusa.com/candidates/kamal/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 23:25:31 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://rageforanusa.com/candidates/kamal/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="manifesto-1--postgraduate-coursework-officer"&gt;Manifesto 1 – Postgraduate Coursework Officer&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Kamal Hassan (he/him)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Master of International Relations&lt;br&gt;
Running with RAGE for ANUSA 2025&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Postgraduate students are the heart of ANU’s teaching and research, yet we are too often treated as an afterthought. From rushed technological changes to declining academic standards and cost-cutting, our learning conditions are at stake. I’m running to ensure that &lt;strong&gt;postgraduates have a strong voice inside ANUSA&lt;/strong&gt; and that ANU delivers the world-class experience we were promised.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item></channel></rss>