<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Home on RAGE for ANUSA</title><link>https://rageforanusa.com/</link><description>Recent content in Home on RAGE for ANUSA</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 23:25:31 +1000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://rageforanusa.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Abigail McCarrol</title><link>https://rageforanusa.com/candidates/abigail/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 23:25:31 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://rageforanusa.com/candidates/abigail/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;More community for smaller degrees&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the College of Arts and Social Sciences there are some very small degrees. As someone who is taking undergraduate public policy, I only know 2 people so far who are doing my degree, and honestly, I am sick of explaining to people in my tutorials what it is. There are many other degrees like this, and in a time when their funding is being cut and they need people to turn to, there is no known community to them. Small or open-ended degrees are hard for students to navigate and plan, and so when they need help with this there is limited support available to them. Or if there is, it&amp;rsquo;s broad and non-specific to their degree. Therefore, I want to ensure that all students can access a community within their degree regardless of its size, and have the opportunities to learn from like-minded people, and receive support that is relevant to their degree and interests.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Ajit Singh</title><link>https://rageforanusa.com/candidates/ajit/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 23:25:31 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://rageforanusa.com/candidates/ajit/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Ankith Arun Aswath</title><link>https://rageforanusa.com/candidates/ankith/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 23:25:31 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://rageforanusa.com/candidates/ankith/</guid><description>&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h1 id="campaign-summary"&gt;Campaign Summary&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hi everyone, I’m Ankith, and I’m excited to re-nominate as your Parents and Carers’ Officer for 2025! Over the past year, I’ve worked hard to strengthen supports for student parents and carers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A key achievement was negotiating changes to the Parents and Carers Grant, making it $1,000 annually instead of per degree, ensuring fairer access. I also developed the &lt;strong&gt;Parents and Carers Information Hub&lt;/strong&gt;, soon to launch, which will centralize university, city, and federal supports. Alongside this, I’ve initiated collaboration with Carers ACT, continued advocacy around EAPs and ECAs, and worked to improve awareness of carer-friendly spaces on campus.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Aoife Foley</title><link>https://rageforanusa.com/candidates/aoife/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 23:25:31 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://rageforanusa.com/candidates/aoife/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Hey I’m Aoife.&lt;br&gt;
I’ve grown up playing Cricket and AFL, so I know how tough it can be navigating girls&amp;rsquo; sport in such male-dominated spaces. I’m super passionate about making sport fun, welcoming, and open to everyone, no matter your skill level or background. I’m a proud player on the ANU Griffins, and honestly, most of my best friends and strongest memories have come from time spent on the sporting field.&lt;br&gt;
Back in high school, I spent most of my time squaring up for girls’ sport; starting new teams, organising guest speakers and events, and perfecting the art of a passive-aggressive email when things needed to get done.&lt;br&gt;
As Gen Rep I’d be committed to strengthening the connection between ANUSA and ANU Sport, so we can build more inclusive and supportive sporting communities on campus. I want to make our sports as fun, open and accessible to everyone as possible.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>April Chesher</title><link>https://rageforanusa.com/candidates/april/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 23:25:31 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://rageforanusa.com/candidates/april/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;My name is April Chesher, I’m a Politics/International Relations student living at the wonderful Burton and Garran Hall, and I am so excited to be running for the position of General Representative in the upcoming 2025 ANUSA elections. I want to deliver an ANU campus that is lively, fun, and safe for everyone.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I understand what it’s like to walk through campus to the Barry Drive bus stop on dark winter mornings and have made the lightless trek back from Civic after a night out. The lack of lighting currently around campus is a dangerous failure of the university that I will work to fix.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Audrey Clementine</title><link>https://rageforanusa.com/candidates/audrey/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 23:25:31 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://rageforanusa.com/candidates/audrey/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Hi! I’m Audrey, a first-year Arts student studying English and living at B&amp;amp;G college. During term time I can usually be found at Badger (pretending to study), Lab (pretending to study), or at Chifley basement actually studying. (Against my will!)&lt;br&gt;
I’m running for Gen Rep because I believe that campus should be more than just functional; it should be comfortable and creative, a place people can congregate socially and have a good time! That’s why my policy focuses on cooling down Uni Ave with better shade, keeping creative spaces (like the Art &amp;amp; Design library!) open for longer and offering something sweet during the summer exam period heat; a free ice cream truck for students! I want to make ANU a place that supports and sustains us beyond the lecture hall; sun-safe, study-safe and sanity-safe. Vote me for a cooler campus! (Literally.)&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Aurora Neumann</title><link>https://rageforanusa.com/candidates/aurora/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 23:25:31 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://rageforanusa.com/candidates/aurora/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Hey ANU! My name is Aurora (she/her) and I am running to be your 2026 ANUSA Education Officer. The ANU’s priority should be the education and research it is globally renowned for, transparency and accountability; I will hold the ANU to account in delivering the quality of education and experience every single student deserves.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As Undergraduate CASS Representative on ANUSA this year, I’ve seen and felt your rage at the position our University is in. I am ready and willing to fight for your education and deliver the representation, support, and transparency every student deserves.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Charley Ellwood</title><link>https://rageforanusa.com/candidates/charley/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 23:25:31 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://rageforanusa.com/candidates/charley/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;My name is Charley Ellwood (he/him), and I am a third year student from the Gold Coast studying a double degree of PPE/Public Policy. I am currently the President of Burgmann College, a Board director for Inspire Tomorrow Education, and the 2025 ANUSA Undergraduate Coursework Officer (UGCO). Having been on the SRC for two years, both as a Gen Rep and now UGCO, I feel immensely passionate about ANUSA, the work we do currently, and the work that we must continue to do. That is exactly why I am running to be your 2026 ANUSA President.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Chith Weliamuna</title><link>https://rageforanusa.com/candidates/chith/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 23:25:31 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://rageforanusa.com/candidates/chith/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="fighting-for-the-education-you-deserve"&gt;Fighting for the education you deserve&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h2 id="no-cuts"&gt;No cuts&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I will &lt;strong&gt;fight for your education&lt;/strong&gt; by standing against the cuts and advocating to reverse Renew ANU in the relevant fora, as well as continuing to support the student and staff protests.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="better-learning-conditions"&gt;Better learning conditions&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I will &lt;strong&gt;fight for your education&lt;/strong&gt; by:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Advocating for smaller tutorial sizes as classes are overcrowded, and demanding the ANU to release their reasoning for making the classes bigger to begin with.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fighting against the DVCA cuts to speed up student support. You deserve extensions and deferrals on time.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Advocating for a student-centred, clear, forward-thinking and accessible AI policy, building on the Gen-AI report.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expanding book and technology bursaries, and creating a new ANUSA learning materials subsidy for students in STEM and the Arts.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id="accessibility"&gt;Accessibility&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Night-time tutorial options and standardised assessment deadlines for students who work full-time or with other commitments.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;BYOD exams where applicable to improve accessibility and bring ANU exams into the 21st century.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expanding the alternative assessments policy to all parts of ANU to improve accessibility, creativity and fairness. You may find your niche here!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id="fairer-assessments"&gt;Fairer assessments&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Flexible weighting options where applicable so that assessments count in ways that benefit the student the most.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Five day simple extensions with lower late penalties in the interim so that you do not have to endure the cost and anxiety of sourcing a doctor last minute.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;More redemptive measures because failing one assessment should not mean you fail the course. I also support strictly limiting hurdle tasks.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Push for clearer assessment rubrics, appeals processes, and preparatory materials like past exams so you are able to give each task your best shot.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h1 id="delivering-the-services-you-need"&gt;Delivering the services you need&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I will &lt;strong&gt;deliver the services you need by:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Darcy Oates</title><link>https://rageforanusa.com/candidates/darcy/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 23:25:31 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://rageforanusa.com/candidates/darcy/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Dylan Ek</title><link>https://rageforanusa.com/candidates/dylan-ek/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 23:25:31 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://rageforanusa.com/candidates/dylan-ek/</guid><description>&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Wider implementation of flexible submission periods across all CBE courses especially for assessments with weightings of 20% or less. This will provide students with the flexibility and support to accommodate obligations outside of university.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mid-semester surveys to improve communication and provide a channel for feedback on tutorial pacing and concerns regarding content and assessments.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tutorial participation via Zoom will be available as a support option for students facing difficulties attending in person. Where there is a participation weighting, to encourage students attending in person, they will receive a 5% participation mark. For those attending via Zoom, the equivalent 5% will be reallocated to the mid-semester exam or assignment.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Dylan Rafel Adams</title><link>https://rageforanusa.com/candidates/dylan/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 23:25:31 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://rageforanusa.com/candidates/dylan/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Hey guys, I’m Dylan, and I’m running to be the Clubs Officer on ANUSA in 2026. I’m passionate about creating the opportunities that clubs need to thrive on this campus.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Campus life and participation have reached their highest levels since post-COVID, which is a fantastic achievement, but it has also highlighted structural issues such as funding shortages and administrative bottlenecks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As the President of one of the ANU’s largest student societies, the International Relations Society, as well as the Marketing Officer of the ANU Jazz Society, I know what it’s like to run a club, big or small. It also means I know what clubs want from our student union.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Edu Setiawan</title><link>https://rageforanusa.com/candidates/edu/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 23:25:31 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://rageforanusa.com/candidates/edu/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Hey, I&amp;rsquo;m Edu (he/him), a first-year arts student and current ressie at B&amp;amp;G. I&amp;rsquo;m running with the RAGE ticket to be one of your General Representatives on ANUSA for next year. With my platform, I&amp;rsquo;ll fight for:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A workable university policy on the use of Generative AI in student assessments to bring our education into the 21st Century.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Improving the social scene on campus through developing options for attracting new F&amp;amp;B outlets to this uni, with particular preference to bringing the first Yo-Chi in Canberra!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Making digital textbooks the norm, and supporting students with the costs of obtaining physical textbooks where possible, to make class resources accessible for all to the greatest possible extent.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expanding usable spaces at the Bryan Kenyon Student Space (BKSS) to make ANUSA, its facilities and the organisation an approachable and useful resource on campus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As a first-year student who also struggles with the stress of our university assessments, it&amp;rsquo;s incredibly important that we have a student union that fights for students&amp;rsquo; academic interests and continually improves its service offerings to meet student needs. That&amp;rsquo;s why I&amp;rsquo;m proud to be running with the RAGE ticket.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Ella Gill</title><link>https://rageforanusa.com/candidates/ella/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 23:25:31 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://rageforanusa.com/candidates/ella/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Eloisa Belmar Osborn</title><link>https://rageforanusa.com/candidates/eloisa/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 23:25:31 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://rageforanusa.com/candidates/eloisa/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;TRANSPARENCY AND PROCESSES&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SSAF POLICY&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
In 2026, ANUSA’s funding agreement is up for negotiation with the university. We currently receive 55% of the student services and amenities fee, known as SSAF. This is student money, and I firmly believe it belongs in student hands. &lt;strong&gt;I will advocate for an increase in the union’s funding&lt;/strong&gt;, while also acknowledging that the university currently uses SSAF money to fund other student services. &lt;strong&gt;We deserve more of our student money in student hands.&lt;/strong&gt; While the university-run services are vital, elected students are best placed to know what students need, and we need to be able to fund this.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Flynn Wade-Schneiders</title><link>https://rageforanusa.com/candidates/flynn/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 23:25:31 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://rageforanusa.com/candidates/flynn/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Indigo Warwick</title><link>https://rageforanusa.com/candidates/indigo/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 23:25:31 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://rageforanusa.com/candidates/indigo/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Isabel Moller</title><link>https://rageforanusa.com/candidates/isabel/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 23:25:31 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://rageforanusa.com/candidates/isabel/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Jess Hayhoe</title><link>https://rageforanusa.com/candidates/jess/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 23:25:31 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://rageforanusa.com/candidates/jess/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Hey ANU, I&amp;rsquo;m Jess and I am running to be your rep for the College of Law, Governance, and Policy in 2025 with RAGE for ANUSA.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As a first-year student studying Laws and International Relations, I am passionate about students being able to have a say in their degrees. I understand how concerning it is watching our education be affected by decisions in which we have little to no input. As CLGP rep, I will fight to put control over our degrees in student hands.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Jessica Prakash</title><link>https://rageforanusa.com/candidates/jessica/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 23:25:31 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://rageforanusa.com/candidates/jessica/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Kamal Hassan</title><link>https://rageforanusa.com/candidates/kamal/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 23:25:31 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://rageforanusa.com/candidates/kamal/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="manifesto-1--postgraduate-coursework-officer"&gt;Manifesto 1 – Postgraduate Coursework Officer&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Kamal Hassan (he/him)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Master of International Relations&lt;br&gt;
Running with RAGE for ANUSA 2025&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Postgraduate students are the heart of ANU’s teaching and research, yet we are too often treated as an afterthought. From rushed technological changes to declining academic standards and cost-cutting, our learning conditions are at stake. I’m running to ensure that &lt;strong&gt;postgraduates have a strong voice inside ANUSA&lt;/strong&gt; and that ANU delivers the world-class experience we were promised.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Lauren Hope-Johnson</title><link>https://rageforanusa.com/candidates/lauren/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 23:25:31 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://rageforanusa.com/candidates/lauren/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Hi everyone! I am super excited to let you know that I’m running to be a college of law rep with RAGE for ANUSA I’m a first year PPE and law student, from Perth and BNG ressie, I’m running because I’ve seen the impact the cuts have had on students and staff.I am running as I would like to make law at ANU a more inclusive environment for all.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My policies include&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Leila Clarke</title><link>https://rageforanusa.com/candidates/leila/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 23:25:31 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://rageforanusa.com/candidates/leila/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Hey! My name is Leila (she/her) and I&amp;rsquo;m running for ANUSA Welfare Officer 2026!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’m a second-year Law &amp;amp; International Relations student, who moved from regional NSW to study at ANU, and I’m angry about the same things you are. I’m also the president of the Refugee Action Campaign, and a social rep at Ursula Hall. Coming from a regional background has shaped my advocacy for Regional, Remote and Rural Students’ (RRRS) issues and directly influenced by policy relating to RRRS rights at ANU. I understand the pressures of living out of home and will work tirelessly to deliver the services you need to relieve cost of living pressures on students. I will work to build a campus where mental health support is prioritised and accessible for all. As Welfare Officer, I will work closely with the departments to drive campaigns and make a difference. I’m particularly excited to work on changing ANU’s SASH policies so they are based on community, with direct student input. Together, we can build a safer, fairer, and more supportive ANU for every student.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Liv Yu</title><link>https://rageforanusa.com/candidates/liv/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 23:25:31 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://rageforanusa.com/candidates/liv/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;HELLO ANU!!! My name is Olivia (Liv) and I am more than excited to run on ANUSA with &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RAGE&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt; as your General Representative. Currently studying a Bachelors in Law &amp;amp; Political Science, I have always had a massive passion in politics, particularly concerning feminism and education. This leads to my desire to deliver the services you &lt;strong&gt;need&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;deserve&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;want&lt;/strong&gt;. Hence, in this election, I wish to address and work with university leadership to improve campus safety for women and make it easier for &lt;strong&gt;you&lt;/strong&gt; to afford education.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Max Agnew</title><link>https://rageforanusa.com/candidates/max/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 23:25:31 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://rageforanusa.com/candidates/max/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;HI! I’m Max, I moved from regional South Australia to study at ANU, and I’m committed to being a strong voice for regional students while building a campus that is more sustainable, supportive, and student-focused. That’s why I’m running on three key policies. First, Bring Back Bubblers: students shouldn’t have to rely on expensive bottled water. By installing more accessible, bottle-friendly taps across campus, we can cut plastic waste, save money, and keep everyone hydrated. Second, More Bins on Campus: overflowing rubbish undermines our community and environment. I’ll push for more bins and better signage, making it easier to do the right thing and keep our spaces clean. Finally, Post-Exam Badger Snack Subsidy: exams are stressful, and students deserve the chance to celebrate their hard work with affordable snacks at Badger &amp;amp; Co. Together, these policies will make ANU cleaner, greener, and more enjoyable for all students.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Nelson Sargent</title><link>https://rageforanusa.com/candidates/nelson/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 23:25:31 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://rageforanusa.com/candidates/nelson/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Hi ANU, I’m Nelson, a first-year Political Science student running as a General Representative in this upcoming ANUSA election. I study political science so that I can understand the institutions around us, and their impact on our lives. The ANU is one such institution.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As a student living on campus, I am acutely aware of the importance of Res Coms and their responsibility not least for major events, but for making our home-away-from-home welcoming and inclusive for all people Contempt for students has been shown by the university’s new Res Com model which seeks to standardise structures, control budgets and diminish democracy in our halls.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Noah McMillan</title><link>https://rageforanusa.com/candidates/noah/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 23:25:31 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://rageforanusa.com/candidates/noah/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Hi everyone! My name is Noah McMillan and I am a postgraduate student at the ANU doing a masters in History. I am originally from Jervis Bay, and did my undergrad at the University of Wollongong and I am running to be your postgraduate College of Arts and Social Sciences (CASS) rep for 2026!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Voting is from the 22nd to the 25th of September at &lt;a href="https://www.voteanusa.com/elections/"&gt;https://www.voteanusa.com/elections/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now more than ever it is so important to have strong representation for postgraduate CASS students as the ANU is cutting more and more of our lecturers and supervisors and jeopardising our education.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Ollie Walsh</title><link>https://rageforanusa.com/candidates/ollie/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 23:25:31 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://rageforanusa.com/candidates/ollie/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Oscar Greenfield</title><link>https://rageforanusa.com/candidates/oscar/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 23:25:31 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://rageforanusa.com/candidates/oscar/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Hello! I’m Oscar (he/him), a second year PPE/Math Sci student and I’m running to be your next undergraduate CASS rep with RAGE for ANUSA! As someone who’s angry about some of the ways our university is changing, I’m prepared to advocate and fight for your education.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="no-more-cuts"&gt;No more cuts&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Renew ANU course and job cuts to the College of Arts and Social Sciences need to stop. Students, some of whom have moved across the country to study at the ANU, deserve the education they signed up for. Students are getting less and less choice of what courses they can complete, whilst at the same time tutorial sizes are increasing, reducing the standard of education offered at this university. Mandatory courses are being cut, forcing students to pick between overloading now to complete the course in the last year it will be offered, or to apply for an exemption, neither of which should be expected of students.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Rifah Tasnia Purbita</title><link>https://rageforanusa.com/candidates/rifah/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 23:25:31 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://rageforanusa.com/candidates/rifah/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Postgraduate and international students balance demanding studies, work, and visas while adapting to a new country, yet their voices are often overlooked. As a first year MIDEC student, I am committed to ensuring equitable support and opportunities for all coursework students across Law, Governance &amp;amp; Policy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My priorities are:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Equitable Careers:&lt;/strong&gt; Advocate for tailored career expo, internships, and pathways into law, governance, security, and policy roles.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Interdisciplinary Opportunities:&lt;/strong&gt; Promote collaboration across schools under CLGP through joint seminars and policy projects.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Research &amp;amp; Mentorship:&lt;/strong&gt; Strengthen access to faculty, alumni, and research networks for coursework students to help build their academic and professional credentials.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Increased Support &amp;amp; Skills:&lt;/strong&gt; Expand health and wellbeing initiatives; as well as academic writing, legal research, and policy skills workshops tailored to international and postgraduate students.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Accessible Learning:&lt;/strong&gt; Campaign for affordable textbooks, more e-texts, and extended library access.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Transparency:&lt;/strong&gt; Establish regular postgraduate forums and surveys to ensure our voices are heard.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Vote Rifah Tasnia Purbita for Postgraduate CLGP representative.
Vote RAGE for ANUSA&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Seamus Giveen</title><link>https://rageforanusa.com/candidates/seamus/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 23:25:31 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://rageforanusa.com/candidates/seamus/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Siddarth Nair</title><link>https://rageforanusa.com/candidates/siddarth/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 23:25:31 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://rageforanusa.com/candidates/siddarth/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Sophie Kington</title><link>https://rageforanusa.com/candidates/sophie/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 23:25:31 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://rageforanusa.com/candidates/sophie/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Throughout my three years at ANU living and learning on this campus, I have become passionate about advocating for ANU students, especially in my role as Residential Mentor at Fenner this year. I am so excited to channel my passion into the General Secretary role working alongside the rest of the team at &lt;em&gt;RAGE&lt;/em&gt; for &lt;em&gt;ANUSA&lt;/em&gt;. I am committed to increasing transparency, consistency, accountability and accessibility within the ANUSA governance processes, actively ensuring ANUSA serves the students at our university. Therefore, as General Secretary I promise a collaborative and engaging system of governance, so students are confident in, and aware of, the decisions affecting them. &lt;em&gt;RAGE&lt;/em&gt; is angry about the same things you are. As a team we will work transparently to bring about concrete change providing students with the education and experience they need, want and deserve. We will shift the focus back to students particularly fighting for quality and equity in educational access by resisting the Renew ANU model, particularly the course cuts, as well as fighting for our res-coms and social life.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Stella Serrao-Smith</title><link>https://rageforanusa.com/candidates/stella/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 23:25:31 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://rageforanusa.com/candidates/stella/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Hey there! I’m Stella (she/her), and I’m running to be your 2026 Vice President with RAGE. I’m a third year Security Studies and Arts student, and over the past two years I’ve been heavily involved with college Residents’ Committees and student life, having been Burton and Garran Hall’s Secretary in 2024 and College President in 2025.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As a result of this involvement, I’m intimately aware of the relationship between regular students, ANU departments and ANUSA. I’ve experienced how difficult it can be to navigate the ANU’s bureaucracy and systems, from financial support to wellbeing services to educational processes. As it stands, our services are not effectively reaching those who need them most, which means our services are underutilised and our voices aren’t heard. ANUSA works best when students understand its services and find it an approachable and welcoming space for all; as your Vice President, I endeavor to bridge the gap between students and representatives.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Suki Waddel</title><link>https://rageforanusa.com/candidates/suki/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 23:25:31 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://rageforanusa.com/candidates/suki/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;My name is Suki and I’m running for ANUSA General Representative in 2025. As a Gen Rep on
the RAGE Ticket, I am committed to delivering the services you need, building the campus you
want, and fighting for the education you deserve.
I’m a first-year Law and PPE student, originally from Sydney, and I’m passionate about getting
involved in student politics. I want to be part of a team that not only supports student voices and
concerns, but also acts on them.
If elected, I will remain committed to the policies I’ve outlined, while also being adaptable and
responsive to other issues brought to me by you, the students.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Suriana Mamone</title><link>https://rageforanusa.com/candidates/suriana/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 23:25:31 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://rageforanusa.com/candidates/suriana/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Hey ANU! My name is Suriana Mamone and I&amp;rsquo;m running to be a College of Science and Medicine (CSM) Representative in Rage for ANUSA 2025. I&amp;rsquo;m deeply passionate about creating a safe and supportive culture for students, especially in demanding and high-pressure degrees such as those in the CSM.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As a second-year Bachelor of Health Science student, I understand how consuming and intense uni can be and without the right support systems and resources in place and available it can be hard to navigate uni on your own. Because of this, a safe and welcoming culture is not just a want, it&amp;rsquo;s a need. Students deserve to feel valued and respected, to feel heard and uplifted.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Tessa McNamara</title><link>https://rageforanusa.com/candidates/tessa/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 23:25:31 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://rageforanusa.com/candidates/tessa/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;CW: Sexual Assault / Sexual Harassment&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hi ANU, I’m Tessa McNamara (she/her) and I’m running to be a GenRep for ANUSA 2026. I believe that it is the responsibility of ANUSA to ensure a safe and comfortable learning environment for the students of ANU, as well as advocating against any cuts to the quality of our education.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As a first year PPE/Arts student from interstate, I’m so grateful for the welcoming community I’ve found at ANU, but understand how tough university life can be. Uni should be a time of learning and socialising, but with stressors like exams, social/financial anxiety and moving away from home, mental health support is vital to students&amp;rsquo; wellbeing and should be protected by your student union.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Tyne Jones</title><link>https://rageforanusa.com/candidates/tyne/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 23:25:31 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://rageforanusa.com/candidates/tyne/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Hey ANU!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My name is &lt;strong&gt;Tyne&lt;/strong&gt;, and I am running to be a &lt;strong&gt;General Representative (Gen Rep)&lt;/strong&gt; on ANUSA. I want to be part of an ANUSA that represents and supports students, so that everyone feels that they are welcome, heard, and part of our campus community.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’m a first year &lt;strong&gt;International Relations and Political Science&lt;/strong&gt; student, passionate about productive government–NFP (not-for-profit) relationships and Australia’s evolving role in the Indo-Pacific. A student from Sydney, I currently work with a government and media relations firm and am a member of the Ku-ring-gai Council Youth Advisory Committee, experiences that have given me insight into effective advocacy, community engagement, and representation.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item></channel></rss>