<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Executive on RAGE for ANUSA</title><link>https://rageforanusa.com/role_types/executive/</link><description>Recent content in Executive on RAGE for ANUSA</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 23:25:31 +1000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://rageforanusa.com/role_types/executive/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aurora Neumann</title><link>https://rageforanusa.com/candidates/aurora/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 23:25:31 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://rageforanusa.com/candidates/aurora/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Hey ANU! My name is Aurora (she/her) and I am running to be your 2026 ANUSA Education Officer. The ANU’s priority should be the education and research it is globally renowned for, transparency and accountability; I will hold the ANU to account in delivering the quality of education and experience every single student deserves.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As Undergraduate CASS Representative on ANUSA this year, I’ve seen and felt your rage at the position our University is in. I am ready and willing to fight for your education and deliver the representation, support, and transparency every student deserves.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Charley Ellwood</title><link>https://rageforanusa.com/candidates/charley/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 23:25:31 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://rageforanusa.com/candidates/charley/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;My name is Charley Ellwood (he/him), and I am a third year student from the Gold Coast studying a double degree of PPE/Public Policy. I am currently the President of Burgmann College, a Board director for Inspire Tomorrow Education, and the 2025 ANUSA Undergraduate Coursework Officer (UGCO). Having been on the SRC for two years, both as a Gen Rep and now UGCO, I feel immensely passionate about ANUSA, the work we do currently, and the work that we must continue to do. That is exactly why I am running to be your 2026 ANUSA President.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Dylan Rafel Adams</title><link>https://rageforanusa.com/candidates/dylan/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 23:25:31 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://rageforanusa.com/candidates/dylan/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Hey guys, I’m Dylan, and I’m running to be the Clubs Officer on ANUSA in 2026. I’m passionate about creating the opportunities that clubs need to thrive on this campus.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Campus life and participation have reached their highest levels since post-COVID, which is a fantastic achievement, but it has also highlighted structural issues such as funding shortages and administrative bottlenecks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As the President of one of the ANU’s largest student societies, the International Relations Society, as well as the Marketing Officer of the ANU Jazz Society, I know what it’s like to run a club, big or small. It also means I know what clubs want from our student union.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Eloisa Belmar Osborn</title><link>https://rageforanusa.com/candidates/eloisa/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 23:25:31 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://rageforanusa.com/candidates/eloisa/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;TRANSPARENCY AND PROCESSES&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SSAF POLICY&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
In 2026, ANUSA’s funding agreement is up for negotiation with the university. We currently receive 55% of the student services and amenities fee, known as SSAF. This is student money, and I firmly believe it belongs in student hands. &lt;strong&gt;I will advocate for an increase in the union’s funding&lt;/strong&gt;, while also acknowledging that the university currently uses SSAF money to fund other student services. &lt;strong&gt;We deserve more of our student money in student hands.&lt;/strong&gt; While the university-run services are vital, elected students are best placed to know what students need, and we need to be able to fund this.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Leila Clarke</title><link>https://rageforanusa.com/candidates/leila/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 23:25:31 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://rageforanusa.com/candidates/leila/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Hey! My name is Leila (she/her) and I&amp;rsquo;m running for ANUSA Welfare Officer 2026!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’m a second-year Law &amp;amp; International Relations student, who moved from regional NSW to study at ANU, and I’m angry about the same things you are. I’m also the president of the Refugee Action Campaign, and a social rep at Ursula Hall. Coming from a regional background has shaped my advocacy for Regional, Remote and Rural Students’ (RRRS) issues and directly influenced by policy relating to RRRS rights at ANU. I understand the pressures of living out of home and will work tirelessly to deliver the services you need to relieve cost of living pressures on students. I will work to build a campus where mental health support is prioritised and accessible for all. As Welfare Officer, I will work closely with the departments to drive campaigns and make a difference. I’m particularly excited to work on changing ANU’s SASH policies so they are based on community, with direct student input. Together, we can build a safer, fairer, and more supportive ANU for every student.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Sophie Kington</title><link>https://rageforanusa.com/candidates/sophie/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 23:25:31 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://rageforanusa.com/candidates/sophie/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Throughout my three years at ANU living and learning on this campus, I have become passionate about advocating for ANU students, especially in my role as Residential Mentor at Fenner this year. I am so excited to channel my passion into the General Secretary role working alongside the rest of the team at &lt;em&gt;RAGE&lt;/em&gt; for &lt;em&gt;ANUSA&lt;/em&gt;. I am committed to increasing transparency, consistency, accountability and accessibility within the ANUSA governance processes, actively ensuring ANUSA serves the students at our university. Therefore, as General Secretary I promise a collaborative and engaging system of governance, so students are confident in, and aware of, the decisions affecting them. &lt;em&gt;RAGE&lt;/em&gt; is angry about the same things you are. As a team we will work transparently to bring about concrete change providing students with the education and experience they need, want and deserve. We will shift the focus back to students particularly fighting for quality and equity in educational access by resisting the Renew ANU model, particularly the course cuts, as well as fighting for our res-coms and social life.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Stella Serrao-Smith</title><link>https://rageforanusa.com/candidates/stella/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 23:25:31 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://rageforanusa.com/candidates/stella/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Hey there! I’m Stella (she/her), and I’m running to be your 2026 Vice President with RAGE. I’m a third year Security Studies and Arts student, and over the past two years I’ve been heavily involved with college Residents’ Committees and student life, having been Burton and Garran Hall’s Secretary in 2024 and College President in 2025.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As a result of this involvement, I’m intimately aware of the relationship between regular students, ANU departments and ANUSA. I’ve experienced how difficult it can be to navigate the ANU’s bureaucracy and systems, from financial support to wellbeing services to educational processes. As it stands, our services are not effectively reaching those who need them most, which means our services are underutilised and our voices aren’t heard. ANUSA works best when students understand its services and find it an approachable and welcoming space for all; as your Vice President, I endeavor to bridge the gap between students and representatives.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item></channel></rss>