<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>College Representative on RAGE for ANUSA</title><link>https://rageforanusa.com/role_types/college-representative/</link><description>Recent content in College Representative on RAGE for ANUSA</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 23:25:31 +1000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://rageforanusa.com/role_types/college-representative/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Abigail McCarrol</title><link>https://rageforanusa.com/candidates/abigail/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 23:25:31 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://rageforanusa.com/candidates/abigail/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;More community for smaller degrees&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the College of Arts and Social Sciences there are some very small degrees. As someone who is taking undergraduate public policy, I only know 2 people so far who are doing my degree, and honestly, I am sick of explaining to people in my tutorials what it is. There are many other degrees like this, and in a time when their funding is being cut and they need people to turn to, there is no known community to them. Small or open-ended degrees are hard for students to navigate and plan, and so when they need help with this there is limited support available to them. Or if there is, it&amp;rsquo;s broad and non-specific to their degree. Therefore, I want to ensure that all students can access a community within their degree regardless of its size, and have the opportunities to learn from like-minded people, and receive support that is relevant to their degree and interests.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Ajit Singh</title><link>https://rageforanusa.com/candidates/ajit/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 23:25:31 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://rageforanusa.com/candidates/ajit/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Darcy Oates</title><link>https://rageforanusa.com/candidates/darcy/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 23:25:31 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://rageforanusa.com/candidates/darcy/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Dylan Ek</title><link>https://rageforanusa.com/candidates/dylan-ek/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 23:25:31 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://rageforanusa.com/candidates/dylan-ek/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Ella Gill</title><link>https://rageforanusa.com/candidates/ella/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 23:25:31 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://rageforanusa.com/candidates/ella/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Jess Hayhoe</title><link>https://rageforanusa.com/candidates/jess/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 23:25:31 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://rageforanusa.com/candidates/jess/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Hey ANU, I&amp;rsquo;m Jess and I am running to be your rep for the College of Law, Governance, and Policy in 2025 with RAGE for ANUSA.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As a first-year student studying Laws and International Relations, I am passionate about students being able to have a say in their degrees. I understand how concerning it is watching our education be affected by decisions in which we have little to no input. As CLGP rep, I will fight to put control over our degrees in student hands.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Jessica Prakash</title><link>https://rageforanusa.com/candidates/jessica/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 23:25:31 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://rageforanusa.com/candidates/jessica/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Lauren Hope-Johnson</title><link>https://rageforanusa.com/candidates/lauren/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 23:25:31 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://rageforanusa.com/candidates/lauren/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Noah McMillan</title><link>https://rageforanusa.com/candidates/noah/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 23:25:31 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://rageforanusa.com/candidates/noah/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Hi everyone! My name is Noah McMillan and I am a postgraduate student at the ANU doing a masters in History. I am originally from Jervis Bay, and did my undergrad at the University of Wollongong and I am running to be your postgraduate College of Arts and Social Sciences (CASS) rep for 2026!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Voting is from the 22nd to the 25th of September at &lt;a href="https://www.voteanusa.com/elections/"&gt;https://www.voteanusa.com/elections/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now more than ever it is so important to have strong representation for postgraduate CASS students as the ANU is cutting more and more of our lecturers and supervisors and jeopardising our education.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Oscar Greenfield</title><link>https://rageforanusa.com/candidates/oscar/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 23:25:31 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://rageforanusa.com/candidates/oscar/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Hello! I’m Oscar (he/him), a second year PPE/Math Sci student and I’m running to be your next undergraduate CASS rep with RAGE for ANUSA! As someone who’s angry about some of the ways our university is changing, I’m prepared to advocate and fight for your education.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="no-more-cuts"&gt;No more cuts&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Renew ANU course and job cuts to the College of Arts and Social Sciences need to stop. Students, some of whom have moved across the country to study at the ANU, deserve the education they signed up for. Students are getting less and less choice of what courses they can complete, whilst at the same time tutorial sizes are increasing, reducing the standard of education offered at this university. Mandatory courses are being cut, forcing students to pick between overloading now to complete the course in the last year it will be offered, or to apply for an exemption, neither of which should be expected of students.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Rifah Tasnia Purbita</title><link>https://rageforanusa.com/candidates/rifah/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 23:25:31 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://rageforanusa.com/candidates/rifah/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Postgraduate and international students balance demanding studies, work, and visas while adapting to a new country, yet their voices are often overlooked. As a first year MIDEC student, I am committed to ensuring equitable support and opportunities for all coursework students across Law, Governance &amp;amp; Policy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My priorities are:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Equitable Careers:&lt;/strong&gt; Advocate for tailored career expo, internships, and pathways into law, governance, security, and policy roles.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Interdisciplinary Opportunities:&lt;/strong&gt; Promote collaboration across schools under CLGP through joint seminars and policy projects.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Research &amp;amp; Mentorship:&lt;/strong&gt; Strengthen access to faculty, alumni, and research networks for coursework students to help build their academic and professional credentials.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Increased Support &amp;amp; Skills:&lt;/strong&gt; Expand health and wellbeing initiatives; as well as academic writing, legal research, and policy skills workshops tailored to international and postgraduate students.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Accessible Learning:&lt;/strong&gt; Campaign for affordable textbooks, more e-texts, and extended library access.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Transparency:&lt;/strong&gt; Establish regular postgraduate forums and surveys to ensure our voices are heard.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Vote Rifah Tasnia Purbita for Postgraduate CLGP representative.
Vote RAGE for ANUSA&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Siddarth Nair</title><link>https://rageforanusa.com/candidates/siddarth/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 23:25:31 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://rageforanusa.com/candidates/siddarth/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Suriana Mamone</title><link>https://rageforanusa.com/candidates/suriana/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 23:25:31 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://rageforanusa.com/candidates/suriana/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Hey ANU! My name is Suriana Mamone and I&amp;rsquo;m running to be a College of Science and Medicine (CSM) Representative in Rage for ANUSA 2025. I&amp;rsquo;m deeply passionate about creating a safe and supportive culture for students, especially in demanding and high-pressure degrees such as those in the CSM.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As a second-year Bachelor of Health Science student, I understand how consuming and intense uni can be and without the right support systems and resources in place and available it can be hard to navigate uni on your own. Because of this, a safe and welcoming culture is not just a want, it&amp;rsquo;s a need. Students deserve to feel valued and respected, to feel heard and uplifted.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item></channel></rss>